Preliminary Guide to the Lisner Auditorium records, 1946-2005 RG0055
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Posters, 1989-1994; RG0055 Series 9; 0.5 Linear feet (Box 2, Box 1)
  - Wonderful World of Louis Armstrong, 10/12/1991 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - An Evening with Madame F, 11/06/1991 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - Master musicians of Jajouka, undated (Box 2, Folder 106)
    Dated Oct. 15
  - Suzanne Westenhoefer, undated (Box 2, Folder 107)
    Dated Oct. 28
  - Suzanne Westenhoefer, undated (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - Multi Kulti, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - Hootie and the Blowfish, undated (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - Hootie and the Blowfish, undated (Box 2, Folder 111)
  - Ballet Folklorico de Chile, 05/04/1994-05/06/1994 (Box 2, Folder 112)
  - Kate Clinton, 02/20/1993 (Box 2, Folder 113)
  - Batimbo of Burundi, 04/21/1991 (Box 2, Folder 114)
  - Dana Carvey, 06/10/1988 (Box 2, Folder 115)
  - Dana Carvey, 06/10/1988 (Box 2, Folder 116)
  - "James Bond: License to Kill" movie poster, 07/10/1989 (Box 2, Folder 117)
  - D.C. Bodybuilding Championships, 06/02/1990 (Box 2, Folder 118)
  - Suzanne Vega, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 119)
  - La Traviata, 11/06/1990 (Box 2, Folder 120)
  - Hungry for Music benefit concert, 09/17/1993 (Box 2, Folder 121)
  - Golpa, 11/12/1994 (Box 2, Folder 122)
  - Carmen Balthrop, 05/19/1991 (Box 2, Folder 123)
  - Marshall Crenshaw, undated (Box 2, Folder 124)
    Dated Dec. 8
  - Los Lobos, undated (Box 2, Folder 125)
    Dated Nov. 9
  - Edie Brickell and New Bohemians, undated (Box 2, Folder 126)
  - Nils Lofgren, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 127)
  - Voices of the Soviet Union, 09/07/1990 (Box 2, Folder 128)
  - Blues and Gospel, Holmes Brothers, Farifield Four, John Dee Holeman, 02/26/1991 (Box 2, Folder 129)
  - Russian Festival Balalaika Concert, 07/07/1990 (Box 2, Folder 130)
  - Peter Allen, undated (Box 2, Folder 131)
    Dated Nov. 16
  - Milton Nascimento, 04/19/1991 (Box 2, Folder 132)
  - Centenial del Natalico de Alfonso Reyes Apr.-Dec. 1989 (Box 2, Folder 133)
  - Alfonso Reyes coloquio, undated (Box 2, Folder 134)
  - Alfonso Reyes, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 135)
  - Evening of Chinese Music, undated (Box 2, Folder 136)
    Dated Jun. 21
  - "My Left Foot" movie poster, 10/30/1990 (Box 2, Folder 137)
  - Perry Payne, 11/13/1993 (Box 2, Folder 138)
  - AIDS benefit comedy show, 06/14/1991 (Box 2, Folder 139)
  - Imperial Bells of China, 04/06/1989-04/09/1989 (Box 2, Folder 140)
  - The Samples, undated (Box 2, Folder 141)
  - KanKouran, 08/31/1991 (Box 2, Folder 142)
  - Celebration of Van Cliburn, 09/28/1992 (Box 2, Folder 143)
  - Peter Allen, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 144)
  - Peter Allen, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 145)
  - Billy Taylor, undated (Box 2, Folder 146)
    Dated Mar. 16
  - Primary Movers, 05/11/1994 (Box 2, Folder 147)
  - Paul Taylor Dance Company, 25th season, undated (Box 2, Folder 148)
    Dated Jan. 15-20
  - The Diary of Black Men, undated (Box 2, Folder 149)
    Dated Feb. 9-10
  - Sankai Juku, undated (Box 2, Folder 150)
    Dated Apr. 19-22
  - Calypso Review, 09/10/1989 (Box 2, Folder 151)
  - Persian Music and Poetry, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 152)
    Dated 1992/08-11
  - Traditional Music of Iran, 07/06/1990 (Box 2, Folder 153)
  - Suzanne Westenhoefer, undated (Box 2, Folder 154)
    Dated Oct. 14
  - Wonderful World of Louis Armstrong, 10/31/1992 (Box 2, Folder 155)
  - Nina Simone, 04/25/1993 (Box 2, Folder 156)
  - Brigham Young University Ballroom Dance Company, 05/29/1991 (Box 2, Folder 157)
- Flyers, 1994-1995; RG0055 Series 10; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series includes performance flyers from 1994-95.
  Formerly ACC#354
  - Andrew Cacho- African Drummers and Dancers, 09/1994 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Martin Berkofsky, 02/1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - A Little Night Music (program and flyer), 03/1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Before Sunrise- free passes, 01/1995 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - P.D. James at the Smithsonian, 02/1995 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - GW School of Medicine Follies, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Korean Friendship Night (flyer and program), 04/1995 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Noa and Gil Dor in concert (program), 04/1995 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Circle of Friends, 03/1995 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Homecoming Talent Show, 02/1995 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Pain, Pain, Go Away (program), 01/1995 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Celebrating Families: In concert with all Ages (Program), 03/1995 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Chen and Dancers- Cancellation flyer, 02/1995 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Martin Berkofsky- cancellation flyer, 02/1995 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Jazz 90, In Tune (program), 02/1995-03/1995 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - The Stone Ring, 03/1995 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Kankouran- Visit Casamance, 09/1994 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - The Paper Bag Players- "'Rubbish!' she cried", 04/1995 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Legal Fiction- Law Revue XVII (program), 1995 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Diz and Duke, 04/1994 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Before Sunrise, 01/1995 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Ballets de San Juan, 06/1994 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - ebi- live in concert, 02/1994 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Benson Bond Moore's Works on Paper, 12/1994-01/1995 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Regional Landscapes, Portraits and Wildlife 1910-1940 (program)
  - The Stone Ring (program), 03/1995 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Valerie Vigoda, 03/1995 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Theatreworks, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Posters, 1995; RG0055 Series 11; 0.25 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series includes performance posters from lisner auditorium from 1995.
  Formerly ACC#355
  - Joe Torry, 02/1995 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Stone Ring, 03/1995-04/1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Noa and Gil Dor in concert, 04/1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Kate Clinton, 03/1995 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Before Sunrise, 01/1995 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Different Faces, One Strong Race, 01/1995-03/1995 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Korean Friendship Night, 04/1995 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Homecoming '95 presents a talent show, 02/1995 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Financial records, 1984-1985; RG0055 Series 12; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series includes financial and work records from 1984-85.
  Formerly ACC#359. Also formerly part of record group 6.5
  - Francis J. Early, Work and Leave Records, 07/01/1984 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Stagehand, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Direct Billings to Leases
  - Proof of check Pick-up, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Frank A. Florentine: Finances, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Postcards from Staff, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Early's name tag, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Flyers, 1984-1994; RG0055 Series 13; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series includes Lisner flyers from 1984-94.
  Formerly ACC#360
  - Homecoming Hop, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Spring
  - KanKouran, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Super Talent Showcase Grand Finals, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Harry Anderson and World Magic Summit, 05/1993 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Rouhollah Khaleghi Orchestra, 03/1990 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Koffi Olomide, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - A Celebration of Van Cilburn, 09/1994 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The National Heritage Fellowship, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Convocation of GW School of Medicine and Health Sciences, 10/1994 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Andrea Chenier, 10/1994 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Ballet Folklorico de Mexico, 10/1994 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Second Genesis- An Afternoon of Celebration, 09/1994 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - A Gift from the Heart to the Children of Lebanon, 10/1994 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Hungry for Music, 09/1994 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Norma, 09/1994 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Contract and Memorandums, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Misc. hatchet and Tearsheets, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Payroll and pay rates, 1983-1986 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Sample tickets- Norma, 09/1994 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Lisner Brochure, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Flyers, photographs, office records, 1968-1990; RG0055 Series 14; 3 Linear feet (Box 2, Box 1)
  This series includes flyers, photos, memos, and financial records from 1968-90.
  Formerly ACC#361
  - Itzhak Perlman, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Lloyd Geisler, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Andre Watts, Adlai Stevenson, Howard Mitchell, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Boris Gutnikov, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Jussi Jalas, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Zino Francesscatti, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Violette Verdy, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Ralph Votapek, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Edward Villella, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Bernadette Laffont, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Itzhak Perlman flyer, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Lisner Financial, 1968-1970 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Memos Sent, 1968-1975 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Washington Ballet, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - IPS and Dep. Slips, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Univ. Cashier: Dept. Deposit Advice, RENTAL, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Univ. Cashier: Coatcheck/ 10 percent Commission Deposits, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Refreshment Sales Deposits, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Security Services, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - IPS, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - PPD, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - EC Work leave, 08/1986-07/1987 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Theatreworks/ USA House manager Booklets and past Brochures, undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Sales Tax Books, 1987-1990 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Financial documents, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Workstudy, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Office records, 1968-1988; RG0055 Series 15; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series includes Lisner programs, tickets, notebook of operations, calendars, news clips from 1968-88.
  Formerly ACC#362
  - 3-D Glasses, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Calendar with Events, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Elwood Emerick Mgt., 1970 ca.-1989 -- --ca. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - F. Early Materials: Postcards, office documents, thesis, notebooks, 1970 ca.-1989 -- --ca. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    includes William L. Clark, "A Historical Study of the Academy Theater in Lynchburg, Virginia." Master's Thesis, East Texas State University, 1970.
  - Tickets and Newspaper- Lisner events, 1970 ca.-1979 -- --ca. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Inward to the Sea (paperweight), undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Assorted tickets and Early Business Cards and Pamphlets, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Parents Weekend, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Harvard in Hollywood, 11/1981 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - National Benefit Society Benefit Ticket, 03/1969 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Itzhak Perlman, 12/1974 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Exhibition of Ceramics, 01/1979 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Festival of Music, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Francescatti, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Dance, 04/1973 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Washington Performing Arts Society, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Capitol Ballet Guild, Inc, 05/1972 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - National Ballet Society Inc: Cinderella, 04/1970 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Tournament Schedule, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Dated June
  - Boris Gutnikov, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Mari-Elizabeth Morgen, 07/1976 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Ralph Votapek, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Bat-Dor Dance Company of Israel, 03/1979 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Ronald Turini, 01/1970 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Jussi Jalas, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Higher Consciousness: A Conference for Spiritual Freedom, 07/1976 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - The Nutcracker, 12/1970-01/1971 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - BI Graduation Ceremony, 06/1976 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - 3rd National Student Film Festival, 11/1968 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Annual Commencement of GW, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Commencement of the Frank W. Ballou High School, 06/1970 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Washington Performing Arts Society, 10/1973 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Wasington Performing Arts Society, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - La Boheme, 03/1970 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Comhaltas Ceoltoiri Eireann, 10/1973 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - GWU Dance Co., undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
    Dated April
  - An Evening with Edward Villella, 06/1970 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Commencement of the Washington Hospital Center: School of Nursing, 06/1970 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Argentina in Concert, 10/1974 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Valentine Day Massacre, 02/1970 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Canterbury Tales, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Concert (Asian-title written in foreign lang.), 10/1974 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Camino a la OTI, undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
    Dated August
  - Christianity in Crisis, 10/1973 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Pamphlets and flyers, 1993-1994; RG0055 Series 16; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series includes program pamphlets and flyers from 1993-94.
  Formerly ACC# 376.
  - Inti-illimani, 12/1994 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Festival of Korea, 09/1993 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Gloria Steinem: Moving Beyond Words, 06/1994 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - KanKouran: Diamono, 09/1993 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    and news release
  - Michael Nyman "The Piano" concerto on Argo, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Shelby Foote's Lecture, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
    sold out announcement
  - NLC registration/Orientation schedule, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Fall
  - The Emptys, 12/1994 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Opening for Hootie and the Blowfish
  - Harvest of Harmony, 11/1994 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - George Winston, 12/1994 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - The Christmas Revels, 12/1994 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    includes paper reviews
- Posters, pamphlets, flyers, 1995; RG0055 Series 17; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1, Box 2)
  This series includes posters, pamphlets, and flyers from 1995.
  Formerly ACC#377
  - Young Dancers of the Washington Ballet, 04/1995 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The GW flute Orchestra, 04/1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Mast Mast, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    postponement notice
  - The National Invitational Choral Festival, 05/1995 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Piano Prodigies from Uzbekistan, 05/1995 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    with "NEWS" media release
  - GW Medicine, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Sousa National High School Honors Band and United States Marine Band in concert, 05/1995 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Memorial Service for Lewis Thompson Preston, 05/1995 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Catch A Fire, 02/1995 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Laurie Anderson, 04/1995 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - The George Washington University Trumpet Ensemble, 04/1995 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - The Keter Betts Jazz Quartet, 03/1995 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - The Piano Choir, 04/1995 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Touro: An Opera of Religious Freedom, 05/1995 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Basketball Diaries, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Gala Guitar Concert, 06/1995 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Programs and posters, 1995; RG0055 Series 18; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series includes programs and posters from 1995.
  Formerly ACC#379
  - Evening with the Classical Guitar, 06/1995 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - GW School of Medicine and Health Sciences Commencement, 05/1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The George Washington University Commencement, 05/1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Nashenas: The Legend of Afghanistan K.L. Siagal's Voice, 05/1995 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Programs and posters, 1989-1995; RG0055 Series 19; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series includes program pamphlets and flyers from 1989-95.
  Formerly ACC# 393.
  - Program - University Band, 11/17/1992 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Program - Ballet Concierto de Puerto Rico, 11/20/1995-11/21/1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Program - The Christmas Revels, 12/1992 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Program - Salute to the Duke, 04/26/1991 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Programs - Parade of the Arts, 11/03/1990 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    2 programs
  - Flyer - Odetta and Women of the Calabash, 01/17/1992 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Flyer - KanKouran, 08/31/1991 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Program - Der Freischutz, 05/03/1991 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Flyer - Sonny Rollins, 12/08/1990 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Programs - Joan Manuel Serrat, 10/12/1992 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Programs - Hungry for Music, 04/15/1992 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Programs - Last Supper at Uncle Tom's Cabin, 04/22/1991-04/23/1991 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Program - Faces of Hope, 04/18/1992 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Flyers - United States Army Chorus, 05/09/1992 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    2 flyers
  - Program - Washington Concert Opera, 04/18/1993-04/20/1993 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Program - Paco Pena/Misa Flamenca, 04/16/1993 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Program - Wonderful World of Satchmo, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Flyer - Vinx, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Program - Washington Ballet Nutcracker, 12/1989 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Posters and programs, 1974-1995; RG0055 Series 20; 1.75 Linear feet (Box 1, Box 2)
  This series includes posters, flyers, invitations, and programs from 1974-95.
  Formerly ACC#418
  - Claude Kipnis, 04/22/1977-04/23/1977 (Box NOT SPECIFIED, Folder 1)
  - The Gypsy Baron: A Comic Opera in Three Acts, 05/22/1982-05/23/1982 (Box NOT SPECIFIED, Folder 2)
  - The Jose Limon Dance Company, undated (Box NOT SPECIFIED, Folder 3)
  - The Nikolais Dance Theatre, March 15-19, undated (Box NOT SPECIFIED, Folder 4)
  - The Paul Taylor Dance Company, January 15-20, undated (Box NOT SPECIFIED, Folder 5)
  - Twyla Tharp Dance Foundation, April 24-26, undated (Box NOT SPECIFIED, Folder 6)
  - CRI: Child Reach International, undated (Box NOT SPECIFIED, Folder 7)
    Elva Darfoor 11 Diamond Elementary
  - Children's Drawings, Child Reach International, undated (Box NOT SPECIFIED, Folder 8)
  - Jesus Christ Superstar, 10/16/1990-10/21/1990 (Box NOT SPECIFIED, Folder 9)
  - Incognito Positivity, undated (Box NOT SPECIFIED, Folder 10)
  - George Winston, December 19, undated (Box NOT SPECIFIED, Folder 11)
    Paper poster. 36" x 49"
  - Junior National Bodybuilding Championship 1 program, 06/23/1995-06/24/1995 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Invitiations to Silvia L. Kohrn retirement reception, 04/28/1994 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    6 invitations
  - Dance Theatre of Harlem program, 08/05/1994-08/06/1994 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Dennis Wolfberg and George Wallace flyers, 09/26/1993 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Comedians. 2 copies
  - National Heritage Fellowships programs, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - World Magic Summit programs, 08/08/1995-08/11/1995 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Junior National Bodybuilding Championship, 06/23/1995-06/24/1995 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Gala Guitar Evening, 06/01/1995 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Carlos Barbosa-Lima, Brazil; Ricardo Cobo, Colombia
  - Hootie and the Blowfish, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Jane and Julia, 04/23/1994 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - David Rousseve, 02/18/1994-02/19/1994 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Subtitle: Reality Urban Scenes, Creole Dreams. 2 copies
  - Betty, 01/20/1989-01/21/1989 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Virgil Fox, 12/06/1985 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Capital Ballet Company February, 02/04/1978 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Jimmy Cliff, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Dated Sept. 21
  - Noa and Gil Dor, 04/28/1995 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Black Belt Spectacular, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Dated April 22. 2 copies
  - Jeff Magee, 04/11/1994 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Merce Cunningham, 03/16/1971 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Missing as of June 2002
  - Pan Masters, 04/09/1994 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Itzhak Perlman, 12/14/1974 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Koffi Olomede, 09/04/1993 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Olatunji [and] Andrew Cacho together, 08/06/1994 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - George Winston, 12/19/1994 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Julian Bream, 10/31/1986 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Gino Vannelli, 12/07/1990 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - 1793 U.S. Capitol 1993 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Mast Mast, 05/06/1995 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- History, program and flyers, 1988; RG0055 Series 21; 1.5 Linear feet
  This series includes information on an exhibit on Lisner's history, Washington National Symphony, programs, and flyers. They are from 1988.
  Formerly ACC#432
  - GWU Lisner Auditorium - "Forty-two Years of Service: An Exhibit of Mementos and Memorabilia", 06/02/1988-07/08/1988 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Lisner - Washington National Symphony, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Lisner - Programs, newspaper clipping, fliers, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Office records, 1953-1985; RG0055 Series 22; 3 Linear feet (Box 2, Box 1)
  This series includes time sheets, payrolls, and public relations memos from 1953-85.
  Formerly ACC#451
  - Frank Florentine Time Sheets, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Sligh, O.D., 08/1953-06/1979 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Payrolls, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    for fiscal year
  - Paychecks signoff book, 02/06/1987-06/03/1988 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Lost and found notebook, 08/01/1988 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    record of both items lost by visitors and items found by Lisner staff. Date listed is date closed
  - Paychecks signoff book, 01/07/1983-08/31/1984 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Paychecks signoff book, 09/09/1984-01/30/1987 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Paychecks signoff book, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Paychecks signoff book, 07/1981-12/1982 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Fenner, John, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
    inactive
  - Frank Florentine- P/R memos, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - James Hamaham, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Kevin Kelly, 09/1979-08/1980 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Payroll - Administrative overtime, 1978-1984 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Posters, 1992-1995; RG0055 Series 23; 0.25 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series includes performance posters from lisner auditorium from 1992-95.
  Formerly ACC#462
  - Postcard: Karen Finley, 11/05/1993 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Program: Inti-illimani, 12/17/1994 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Flyer: Alice in Wonderland, 12/02/1992 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Program and postcard: Concierto para Bolivia, 08/04/1995 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Poster: Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan, 08/26/1995 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Programs and posters, 1995; RG0055 Series 24; .25 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series includes programs, posters and mailers from 1995.
  Formerly ACC#468
  - Program: Gounod's Romeo et Juliette, 06/02/1995-06/04/1995 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Program: Chinese Kung Fu, 08/23/1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Cosi Fan Tutte - Opera International, 08/20/1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Program: 75th Women's Suffrage, 08/24/1995 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Mailers and programs: Noh Theater of Japan, 09/05/1995 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    3 mailers, 2 programs
  - Der Fliegende Holander, 09/08/1995-09/10/1995 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    2 programs. Performances on Sept. 8 and Sept. 10
  - GWU Medical School Convocation, 09/12/1995 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Poster: 4th Annual Hungry for Music Delevantes, 09/16/1995 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Posters and programs, 1995; RG0055 Series 25; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series includes posters and programs from 1995.
  Formerly ACC#483
  - Program: Fourth Hungry for Music Concert, 09/16/1995 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Poster: Fourth Hungry for Music Concert, 09/16/1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Poster: Mr./Ms. America Physique Championship, 10/28/1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Poster: W.C.O. Wagner's Der Fliegende Hollander, 09/08/1995-09/10/1995 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Performances on Sept. 8 and Sept. 10
  - Poster: Welcome Week, 08/24/1995-09/04/1995 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Posters, flyers, programs, 1995; RG0055 Series 26; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series includes posters, flyers, programs, and brochures from 1995.
  Formerly ACC#485
  - Poster: How to Make and American Quilt, 10/06/1995 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Sponsored by the Program Board. 2 copies
  - Season Brochure: Washington Performing Arts Society, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Program: Supreme Council 33 Degrees, 10/09/1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Schedule of Events: Office of Admissions, Campus Life, PSDS, Academic Support Services, 10/13/1995-10/14/0995 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Program: Jajouka, 10/15/1995 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Sponsored by the Concert Society. 2 copies
  - Brochure: Fellowship Awards, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Sponsored by Folk and Traditional Arts Prog. 2 copies
  - Postcard: Jajouka, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Dated Fall. Sponsored by Brian Jones. 2 copies
  - Flyer: Jajouka, 10/15/1995 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Poster: Kaboria, 10/10/1995 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Sponsored by Mirimar. 2 large and 2 small posters